module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'In art, what material does batik use? ', 
    a: 'Wax',
    b: 'Clay',
    c: 'Wood',
    d: 'Beads',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Author George Sand famously dated:', 
    a: 'Liszt',
    b: 'Salieri',
    c: 'Chopin',
    d: 'Satie',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'The Kenai Peninsula is part of what state?', 
    a: 'Michigan',
    b: 'Florida',
    c: 'Massachusetts',
    d: 'Alaska',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Aaliyah appeared in what movie shortly before her death?', 
    a: 'Chicago',
    b: 'Queen of the Damned',
    c: 'Men in Black II',
    d: '8 Mile',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Wood alcohol poisoning can be treated with:', 
    a: 'Booze',
    b: 'Saline',
    c: 'Iodine',
    d: 'Baking Soda',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Benadryl can be used both as an antihistamine and a(n) ______?', 
    a: 'Antiemetic',
    b: 'Anti-inflammatory',
    c: 'Diuretic',
    d: 'Analgesic',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Led Zeppelin wrote songs about the works of which author?', 
    a: 'Nietzsche',
    b: 'Poe',
    c: 'Tolkein',
    d: 'Wagner',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does the Scandinavian liquor Akvavit taste like?', 
    a: 'Cedar',
    b: 'Anise',
    c: 'Elderberry',
    d: 'Pepper',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a combination of diced carrots, celery, and onion called in French cuisine?', 
    a: 'Trois Couleurs',
    b: 'Vraie Poutine',
    c: 'Galette',
    d: 'Mirepoix',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which animal has its testicles above its dingaling?', 
    a: 'Manatee',
    b: 'Armadillo',
    c: 'Kangaroo',
    d: 'Sea Turtle',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];
